cinepolisusa.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting www.cinepolisusa.com. We value our customers and are committed to responsible privacy practices.

California Cinema Investments Inc. operates this website/site ([http://www.cinepolisusa.com](http://www.cinepolisusa.com/)) (the “Site”) and the digital platforms (by using mobile devices such as iPhone®, iPad®, BlackBerry®, Android® and any other platforms or devices, web sites or micro websites used by us) (“Digital Platforms”), and this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) discloses the privacy practices for this website and for the digital platforms and the related services and activities offered through them (collectively referred to as our “Site” and/or “Digital Platforms”). California Cinema Investments Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively referred to as “Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas”, “us”, “we” and “our”) are dedicated to your online privacy.

This Policy is subject to and fully incorporates our Site and Digital Platforms Terms of Use (http://www.cinepolisusa.com/home/terms). By accessing and using our Site and Digital Platforms, you agree to be bound by all the terms and conditions of this Policy and the Site Terms of Use. If you do not agree to be bound to these terms and conditions and Policy, do not access or use our Site or Digital Platforms.

 **Please read the following carefully.**

  1. What information do we collect from you?
  2. Where and when do we collect information and how do we use it?
  3. How do we respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals?
  4. With whom do we share information we collect from you?
  5. How can you review, revise or delete information we collect from you?
  6. Can you opt-out of receiving communications from us?
  7. What security protections are in place to protect information collected by us?
  8. Do we use “cookies” and other information gathering technologies?
  9. Do we collect information from children?
  10. What you need to know about third-party sites and digital platforms, and other privacy policies.
  11. What else you need to know about this Policy.
  12. Your California Privacy Rights.
  13. Contact us.

##### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

We collect two categories of information from users of our Site and Digital Platforms — “Personally Identifiable Information” and “Non-Personally Identifiable Information”. We collect this information so that we can offer you our services and products and give you an efficient and customized experience with our Site and Digital Platforms.

“ _Personally Identifiable Information_ ” is information you voluntarily give us that specifically identifies you.

When you create or register an account, purchase products or services, participate in any of our programs, send us questions or feedback, register your e-mail address with us, communicate with us, or otherwise participate in our Site and in our Digital Platforms, we may ask you to give us information about yourself. You have the option to use our Site or Digital Platforms, and if you do use our Site or Digital Platforms, we will ask you to give us and we will collect the following Personally Identifiable Information: your first and last name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, payment method and other information once it is associated with you and your transaction. We may also collect information about your movie preferences, your purchases and information you disclose to the general public through review pages, blogs and message boards. This Policy refers to this personal information as “Personally Identifiable Information”.

“ _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_ ” is information that does not identify you or any specific person.

When you visit our Site or Digital Platforms, we automatically collect information relevant to your visit, such as the frequency and length of your visit to our Site or Digital Platforms, what website you came from, the search engine you used, which website you go to next, what web browser and operating system you use, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. Again, this non-personal information is not associated with any specific individual. This Policy refers to this non-personal information as “Non-Personally Identifiable Information”.

##### 2\. WHERE AND WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION AND HOW DO WE USE IT?

We may collect Personally Identifiable Information when (a) you participate in our Site and Digital Platforms, such as when you create or register an account, purchase products or services, participate in any of our programs, send us questions or feedback, register your e-mail address with us, communicate with us, or otherwise participate in our Site or Digital Platforms; and (b) if you wish to purchase certain products and services in our theaters (i.e. gift cards, loyalty/award cards, memberships, etc.).

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information for the purposes for which you provided it to us, such as providing you with our products and services, and enhancing the quality of our Site or Digital Platforms for you. We will also use your Personally Identifiable Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts and to customize our Site’s and Digital Platforms’ content and services for you and all of our customers. Sometimes we will use your Personally Identifiable Information to notify you of important changes to this Policy, and to send you news, offers and savings related to our products and services.

Sometimes, we might combine or supplement your Personally Identifiable Information with information we receive from our affiliates or third-party providers. If we do combine or supplement your Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat all of that information as covered by this Policy.

We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you visit our Site or Digital Platforms. Additionally, we may engage third-party providers or advertisers to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information and share that non-personal information with us. This Non-Personally Identifiable Information is not specific to you and may be aggregated with Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected from other users.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to improve our Site or Digital Platforms and troubleshoot issues related to our Site and Digital Platforms, such as our servers and software. We also use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to better understand our Site or Digital Platforms and user demographics, to provide you products and services purchased (and/or to improve them), and provide advertisements that may be of interest to you.

##### 3\. HOW DO WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS?

Cinépolis does not tracks its customers and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.

##### 4\. WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

We share Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information among ourselves, such as with our Mexico-based parent company, Cinépolis de México S.A. de C.V., and other corporate affiliates and subsidiaries. We also share Personally Identifiable Information with our service providers (i.e. marketing and advertisement agencies, banks, processing agents and distribution institutions), partners and third-party services providers to deliver to you the products or services you have requested. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the products and services purchased on our Site and Digital Platforms or give your address to the delivery service company so they can deliver your product to you. We will encourage our third-party service providers and partners to respect your privacy, but we (and you acknowledge that we) cannot control how they use your Personally Identifiable Information and this Policy does not govern their use of your Personally Identifiable Information.

When we share your Personally Identifiable Information among our affiliates and subsidiaries, your Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred outside of the United States of America. If you do not want us to transfer your Personally Identifiable Information outside of the United States of America, do not give us your Personally Identifiable Information.

If we later decide that we want to sell, rent or otherwise transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to others who are not our affiliates, subsidiaries, or authorized third-party service providers or partners, we will first get your permission. If you opt-in to receive communications from us and our third-party service providers and partners, we will share your Personally Identifiable Information as necessary to supply you with those communications.

We may share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with third-party advertisers or other parties outside ourselves to improve our Site and Digital Platforms, and enhance your online experience. Again, this Non-Personally Identifiable Information is not specific to you and does not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

If you have authorized third-parties, such as a social networking services like Facebook or Twitter, to gather information about your activities on our Site or Digital Platforms (e.g., to notify your friends that you have purchased movie tickets), we may share Personally Identifiable Information with these third-parties as previously authorized by you.

As part of our ongoing business operations, we may transfer Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information as part of a business transaction, such as a merger or corporate purchase and sale. In this connection, your Personally Identifiable Information will be treated as a business asset and possibly transferred to a business that will control or own us and our assets.

Sometimes we might be required by law to share your Personally Identifiable Information with others, such as in response to a court order, subpoena or government investigation. Also, we reserve the right to share your Personally Identifiable Information with others when we believe it is reasonably necessary to protect others and ourselves.

Your California Privacy Rights. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors of our Site and Digital Platforms who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes. You have the right to request information regarding such disclosure by contacting us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.). All such requests must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the e-mail subject line or envelope or post card, and you must include your name, address and e-mail address.

##### 5\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, REVISE OR DELETE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

We understand that your Personally Identifiable Information is important to you. You always have the right to ask us for a copy of the Personally Identifiable Information you have given to us. Additionally, you can review and revise your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and changing your personal information, or by asking us to revise your Personally Identifiable Information.

For any question, deletion or modification request regarding your Personal Identifiable Information, you must send us attached to each question or request, your personal identification (official ID issued by a competent authority) (“ID”), in order to verify your identity and guarantee the correct privacy and use of your information and Personal Identifiable Information.

If you want us to delete your Personally Identifiable Information, tell us so. However, some of your Personally Identifiable Information, such as your transaction history on our Site or Digital Platforms, cannot be deleted. If you request us to revise or delete your Personally Identifiable Information, you may not be able to access all of the features of our Site or Digital Platforms.

To receive a copy of, to request us to revise or request us to delete your Personally Identifiable Information, please write or e-mail us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or privacypolicy@cinepolis.com. All such requests must be labeled “ _My Personally Identifiable Information Request_ ” on the e-mail subject line or on the envelope or post card, and you must include your name, ID, address and e-mail address. When you contact us regarding your Personally Identifiable Information, we will first need to verify your identity before releasing your Personally Identifiable Information to you. If you make such a request, we will respond within a reasonable time.

##### 6\. CAN YOU OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING COMMUNICATIONS FROM US?

We and our third-party services providers and partners may occasionally send you e-mails and other communications regarding our products and services. Additionally, when you participate in our Site or Digital Platforms, such as register an account, purchase products or services, or register your e-mail address with us, we may ask you if you want to receive communications from us and our services providers.

If you do not want to receive communications from us or our third-party service providers and partners, tell us so when you register an account, purchase products or services or otherwise participate in our Site and Digital Platforms. At any time, you can opt-out from receiving communications from us or our third-party service providers or partners by writing or e-mailing us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.). All such requests must be labeled “ _Communication Opt-Out_ ” on the e-mail subject line or on the envelope or post card, and you must include your name, address and e-mail address.

If you opt-out from receiving communications from us and our service providers, we will implement your request within a reasonable time. However, your decision to opt-out will not affect our communications with you to complete your transactions or fulfill your requests, such as a movie ticket purchase or other ministerial/administrative communications.

##### 7\. WHAT SECURITY PROTECTIONS ARE IN PLACE TO PROTECT INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US?

We realize that you must trust us when you give us your Personally Identifiable Information and we value your trust. Accordingly, we protect data transmissions to and from our Site with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). We take other reasonable measures to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, such as requiring you to use a password for your account, storing all of your Personally Identifiable Information in encrypted files, and taking procedural and managerial steps within our companies to try to protect against the loss, misappropriation or alteration of your Personally Identifiable Information.

Additionally, credit card transactions and order fulfillment may be handled by established third- party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. If we use these third-party service providers, we will give them Personally Identifiable Information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and deliver your order.

Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, but by using our Site and Digital Platforms you acknowledge that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control. The security, integrity and privacy of any information and data exchanged between you and our Site or Digital Platforms cannot be guaranteed, and any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third-party.

When we share your Personally Identifiable Information with nonaffiliated third-parties, we will require these third-parties to take reasonable measures to protect your Personally Identifiable Information.

##### 8\. DO WE USE “COOKIES” AND OTHER INFORMATION GATHERING TECHNOLOGIES?

Yes, we use “cookies.” Cookies are a standard feature found in most websites on the Internet. Cookies are small files deployed from a website, like our Site and Digital Platforms, and placed on your hard drive. These files allow us to gather information about how and when visitors use our Site and Digital Platforms so we can, among other things, understand our user demographics, deliver relevant advertisements, and administer our Site and Digital Platforms. Cookies supply us with information such as the frequency and length of your visit to our Site and Digital Platforms, what website you came from, the search engine you used, which website you go to next, what web browser and operating system you use, and your IP address. Additionally, these files help us “remember” you and your preferences, so you don’t have to re-enter information about yourself, like your User ID and Password and your preferences. Cookies make your use of our Site and Digital Platforms easier, make our Site and Digital Platforms run more smoothly and help us to maintain security. Your web browser may give you the option to disable or erase our cookies. You are free to disable and erase our cookies. However, if you do so, our Site and Digital Platforms may not work properly.

Our Site and Digital Platforms may also use web beacons or transparent GIFs (invisible files stored on web pages) to, among other things, access cookies and count users who visit our Site and Digital Platforms. Additionally, we may in the future use other information gathering technologies in connection with our Site and Digital Platforms.

We may permit third-party advertisers to place advertisements and links on our Site and Digital Platforms. When you click on an advertisement or link on our Site or Digital Platforms, these third- party advertisers may use cookies, web beacons and other information gathering technologies to gather information about you. We do not and cannot (and you acknowledge that we do not and cannot) control how these third-parties use Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected from you. These third-parties have their own privacy policies and disclosure practices that may be different from this Policy. We are not responsible for the actions of these third-parties. Please contact these third-parties directly and ask them about their privacy policies and disclosure practices.

##### 9\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN?

We take the protection, privacy and safety of children very seriously. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, without first receiving verifiable parental consent we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. For this purpose, we have created special policies for the collection of information from children under 13 years of age (“children” or “child”).

Before a child is permitted to use certain features of our Site and Digital Platforms, such as register for an account, purchase products or services, or communicate with us, and before we collect a child’s Personally Identifiable Information through our Site and Digital Platforms, we must first obtain verifiable consent from the child’s parent. The parental consent must be completed on the form provided here (http://www.cinepolisusa.com/docs/Parental-Consent-Form.pdf). The completed parental consent form must be delivered by first class mail or by e-mail to Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.). All such consent forms must be labeled “ _Children’s Privacy Policy – Parental Consent_ ” in the e-mail subject line or on the envelope or post card, and you must include your name, ID, address and e-mail address, also a document in which establishes that you are the child´s parent. Once we have verified that you are the child’s parent, we will send you an e- mail stating so and confirming your consent.

Once we obtain parental consent, we will only use the child’s Personally Identifiable Information for those purposes for which it was provided. We do not disclose a child’s Personally Identifiable Information outside of ourselves and our third-party service providers and partners. We will not condition a child’s participation with our Site and Digital Platforms on the child disclosing more Personally Identifiable Information than is reasonable necessary to participate with features of our Site or Digital Platforms.

You as the parent have the right at all times to review and revise the Personally Identifiable Information we have collected from your child. You can ask us for a copy of your child’s Personally Identifiable Information. You can also ask us to revise or delete your child’s Personally Identifiable Information. However, some of your child’s Personally Identifiable Information, such as transaction history on our Site or Digital Platforms, cannot be deleted. If you request us to revise or delete your child’s Personally Identifiable Information, your child may not be able to access all of the features of our Site or Digital Platforms.

To receive a copy of, to request us to revise or request us to delete your child’s Personally Identifiable Information, please write or e-mail us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.). All such requests must be labeled “ _My Child’s Personally Identifiable Information Request_ ” in the e-mail subject line or on the envelope or post card, and you must include your name, ID, address and e-mail address. When you contact us regarding your child’s Personally Identifiable Information, we will first need to verify your identity before releasing your child’s Personally Identifiable Information to you.

Unless modified by these special child policies, all other terms and conditions of this Policy apply to a child’s Personally Identifiable Information.

##### 10\. WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THIRD-PARTY SITES OR DIGITAL PLATFORMS, AND OTHER PRIVACY POLICIES.

This Policy only covers Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you through this Site – www.cinepolisusa.com or through our Digital Platforms. Other websites and third-parties accessible through our Site or Digital Platforms may have privacy policies and disclosure practices that are different from this Policy. We are not responsible for the actions of these other websites and third-parties. Please contact these websites and third-parties directly to learn about their privacy policies and disclosure practices.

##### 11\. WHAT ELSE YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THIS POLICY.

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any modifications to this Policy will be effective upon delivery of notice to you or upon our prominently posting a notice of such modification to this Policy. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the address you have provided to us and/or posting a notice or notification on our Site or Digital Platforms. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid e-mail address as a registered user of our Site or Digital Platforms, review our Site and Digital Platforms covered by this Policy and be aware of any modifications to this Policy.

This Policy covers all Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected by us through our Site and Digital Platforms. This Policy does not cover any information we collect outside of our Site and Digital Platforms or information you share in any public space or domain, such as a blog, review page, or message board. Information you disclose to the general public may be gathered by third-parties who may use that information. We cannot control how these third-parties use that information you disclose to the general public and you assume any and all risk of disclosing that information.

##### 12\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.

If you are a California resident, you can request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Cinépolis to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us by writing or e-mailing us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.).

##### 13\. CONTACT US.

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to give us feedback, please contact us by writing or e-mailing us at Cinépolis Luxury Cinemas, Attention: Privacy Manager, at: 14951 North Dallas Parkway Suite 300, Addison, Texas 75254 or [privacypolicy@cinepolis.com](mailto:privacypolicy@cinepolis.com.).

Effective Date: This Policy is effective immediately. Last Updated: February 16, 2016.
